Hello hello so friends in this video I am going to
talk about such people
friends insurance company
is a company of insurance sector it is a very
good company friends in this video I am going to
tell that it can give
us multibagger returns whether at this
valuation we should enter into it or whether
it is a good stock to make profit in short term or
not
friends I am going to answer many questions in this
video friends friends
if you are new to my channel then
please subscribe to my channel
I keep uploading share market related
and state and interesting videos on
my channel friends if you have
any question related to share market
then you can ask me in the comment box
I answer every comment personally friends friends
let's talk
about this long sector
friends
before making any investment in any stock it is very important for us to know about the
role model of that company its fundamentals its history so
friends this is an
ICC fox company its value is
number I General Insurance Company Limited
friends this company is  I will
find it in 2001 in Mumbai, friends, this bank is
its parent company, friends, okay
friends, like HDFC Bank, HDFC Life
Insurance Company, it has
subscription, so friends, this company
works in multiple, therefore friends, this
company is working in this company by subscribing to motor insurance, property
tax liability,
friends, this company is
quite better, friends, the development
of a
flying nation, friends, in the
developed countries outside, actually there is an insurance
sector in insurance,
which is quite big, the people who are in the insurance
sector, friends, every person is
good, so if we talk about population, then
7275 percent of the population is safe,
in India, the percentage of that sector, friends, when that
percentage is only two or three percent, then the
sector which used to grow
tremendously, before there used to be India Insurance Company,
whose name is, so I
subscribe to companies in it and
I think it will do a lot, the
share of this company, friends, here the
market of this company
is 21 percent, friends, how much
70% this year
This company has a huge market share, that is,
in liability insurance, friends, the company has a
market share of 14%, friends, and
in marine insurance, it is 30%,
friends, it is quite good, friends,
if we talk about the revenues for this, then
friends, from motor insurance, motor
insurance means the loan that we take,
friends, they take loan for car or two wheeler,
its
insurance company gets 60% revenue,
friends, and I would like health insurance agents,
corporates will like this, the
entire source of them is coming from India only,
friends, friends,
if we talk here, the
company gets less from government guarantee bails from the government, that is the
role model of that company,
it is very good, there
is full chance of becoming a multiplayer in future, friends,
I feel like this, friends, if you look at
some of the key points of its shares, if we
talk about this, then it
is quite on the side till 2017, friends, the price is
much above the bad, this company is straight, the
price of 9.41 is Suresh, friends, it
gives very little division, zero point  In 2017,
friends, the market cap of large cap companies
is 5000 and its backbone is
ICC Bank. Friends, it is very good.
Friends, if you look here today,
0.5 company share market in it. Friends, today there was about
300 collections but there was
not much decline in it. Friends, if we talk about the life insurance
companies, there was not much decline in it.
In today's section,
friends, here it has given about 475 negative
returns. If we talk about one month,
friends, then negative 1.94 means
it has made a negative return of 2%. If we
talk about one year, then it has made a negative return of 2%.
Friends, its listing is
not very old. If there is a
list of such actors, then here
2000 means in the last two-three years itself,
you can see that it has given a return of 80 percent, which is
quite good.
Friends, it is a very good marvel. Friends, if you
look at the price forecast here, it has marked
20 percent for the coming years.
Sixty-five percent of that
list has been created by creating an A.  Hey friends, the
side here is this person side of Rs 1634
and the medium side is
showing subsidy and the price can be above 1473
and the lower side can go
out at 912, that is, at 27,
friends, here the lower side and the higher
side are visible in a little bit,
friends, if I feel that
in the coming few years it can give multibagger returns,
where is my tab like this,
friends, let's look at the financials, the company's
profit definition has increased a lot, friends,
friends, at 18 per 18, 1880 means you
can say that the company has grown by 98%, according to friends,
if you loot, then according to 8880 crores, friends, this year it has increased to 12450 crores,
friends, if we talk about the meeting here, then the
net income is also increasing, it has increased
from 861 crores to 1193 crores in
an interview, friends,
you can see the running share right now, friends, there has been
no decrease in Curitiba Uzbekistan.
Here you can see that the 2016
IPS has increased, friends, that is much better,
friends, you could have watched the free channels,
friends, the company has a free Qty of Rs 3129 crore,
which is a very good thing, friends, this is a
trick, so I will tell you that when there are
problems within the company, there are problems within the market,
like in a well
because of the court, if there is a
problem in India, then the company
needs capital to rescue it, so okay, whatever it is, it
helps the company at that time,
friends, let's see its companies here,
who are they, friends, HDFC Life, Bajaj
Finserv and this Way Live, all these companies
are good companies, friends, all the companies are
very solid companies, friends, if
any company is available at the lowest valuation, then it is
Silicon Valley, here you
can see its price, but
HDFC Life is eighth, Bajaj Finserv is
27th - of all the companies, it is the
second life insurance company, SBI, its
TV shift,
hello friends, Pihu, it is not very important,
please, if it happens more then it
is the company  Nothing like this happens on valuation, so I
want to tell you that this should be confirmed daily, clarification should be given, secondly let's
look at the holding pattern, friends, the
holding pattern is very important, the
promoter has a holding of 51 percent,
a mutual fund has 50
percent voting and you can clearly see that the
mutual fund has bought more than double the stock in it,
second ODI has a
building of 14%
that points 226 percent, let's see the
lineage breakdown, did the stock sell or buy,
friends, this has a big folding in it,
friends, if we look at the practice, friends, the
share quality is very big,
friends, friends, I always see that in the stock which is there, other
parties, that is, retail investors, have very little
investment, friends, here 7.1
more shares are very good, they have the
potential to make multibagger returns in the future,
friends, you should see at
which price should we enter in it,
friends, this price which is going on is looking a
little bit weak, I am a little
side, right now friends, I feel that if it goes
below 1100 in this market  If
you get it below 11 eyes, then we should
definitely take entry in it. Right now it is
getting a good price as well, friends, it is
getting at a very good price even below 11 and
12 shares. If we get this share, then
we should enter in it, or
below 12, I would say you
can take entry in it, friends, I
feel that in the coming few
days, when the market falls, then now
we will get a chance to regulate this city at a good price.
If you keep one thing in
mind, the shares are very big, it can
become a multi-millionaire in future, whoever has it, do
not forget it in the daily, friends, in future it will make
us a very good return, it will
give hundred percent, friends, this is
also in my portfolio, friends, thank you so much
for watching this video.